LAURA CRONIN



Professional Skills:

JavaScript and ReactJS
HTML5 and CSS3
Java, C#, Python and SQL
Analyse software
requirements
Create technical
documentation
UI Design
UX
Mobile applications
Testing and debugging
GitHub and GitFlow

Personal Skills:

Reliable and professional
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated
Communication
Interpersonal skills
Organisation
Time management
Flexibility

Email: <u>cronin.laura91@gmail.com</u>

Phone: 0422236518

Address: Manly, Sydney 2095

ABOUT ME

I am currently working as a metadata engineer on a metadata management system for IAG. I am the sole front-end developer of this system, working predominantly with React. Previously, I was a Primary Teacher for 5 years, however was looking to broaden my horizons and take the next step in my career with my computer programming knowledge. My passion for learning inspires me to continually gain new skills. My next goal is to further develop my web development skills and nurture my curiosity and passion for coding. Visit my profile to learn more about me and access my projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019-2020 – **Metadata engineer** at IAG 2019-2020 – **Intern developer** at IAG 2017-2018 - **Full-time Classroom Teacher** on Years 5 and 6 at St. Kieran's Manly Vale 2014-2016 – **Full-time Classroom Teacher** on Year 4 at St. Joseph's Narrabeen

EDUCATION

Continuous self-directed learning around web development 2019 - CertIV in Programming, Open Colleges Australia 2016 - Graduate Certificate in Theology, Broken Bay Institute 2013 – Bachelor of Teaching (Primary)/Bachelor of Arts, University of Newcastle, GPA: 6.4 / 7 2008 - High School Certificate, St. Francis Xavier's College, Hamilton, UAI/ATAR: 92.5